Thank you.
Okay, there we are. That's good to say.
And so, good morning.
I was thinking this morning, it was, get a lot of this, it was 13 years ago that I reached through last.
And good memories on that one.
I hate to say, it is strange standing up here, but I get to say that this is the first time I've ever spoken in a room.
That is standing room only.
So that's, that's the answer, right?
And with that, in fact, that is probably like the standing room that I just got.
So, I'll take both of those.
I actually was describing to my son this morning the service.
And he was home visiting just over nine, and I'm distraughting it.
And I'm like, if you're a part of the site, you're not going to be in a fit, and it's been a rose of clothes.
And so, my son likes to give me advice, and he goes, well, ho, ho, dad.
No, it's yours.
You're going to have to lock that up.
So, I'm going to do my best to end this morning working.
I still will work sometimes.
So, I have to say, though, it really is something.
And guys, we're doing these Advent weeks.
The half this week, where our focus is on love, fall on, watch Sunday.
Because there's a part of me that just feels unquiet.
You know, we're thinking of amazing preaching God's word.
That's also amazing, transforming.
But there's something about after doing.
And that's what we're doing this week.
We're serving.
It is Christ-like love in our city.
And I feel like that's probably the truest form of the church.
So, it's kind of cool that line up this way.
That's what we're talking about.
And we're actually going to have a chance to do that today.
And I want to freak you out.
But part of what I want to do today is give us all a chance, just a few minutes,
to honestly serve and love like Christ.
And we're going to take that stuff today.
So, not all the people in this room probably have all done this before.
There's something special about Advent, love, and serving on the same moment.
So, as we do that, as we get ready for that, let me pray for us.
And then we'll jump in with just a couple verses.
So, let's pray.
So, Father God, as we endeavoring that through the Advent season, love, joy, hope, and to be focused on love,
we are mindful that things are more than just qualities.
These are things that you've drawn to our world through your son.
So, Father God, we want to remember, focus on love, we want to anticipate celebrating the grace of Jesus,
understanding all that it means.
So, Father God, today, we pray that you would remind us, focus,
that you would help us to get the greatest love story that you've ever been told.
The story of your son.
The family that is an infant.
God Almighty, creator of all, pretty much glad.
So, Lord, we pray that you would have his gun.
We pray this in Jesus' name.
Amen.
And as I say, it really is the greatest story that has ever been told.
No fiction, right?
It's the greatest story.
And isn't it amazing?
It somehow has gotten missed to them.
But it does minimize, in some instances, this news.
I don't know if you could say it's even better news.
If you were to go and do a public poll and say,
what is in the top ten of most famous, but most meaningful love stories?
Or if you were to Google it, like I did.
Do you know that the story of Jesus, the story of God's love is pursued in mankind,
it doesn't even make the top ten of us.
Some of us know that in our number of the world, we've missed it.
We've missed it.
So, what do we do with that?
Well, I'm just going to say, hold the story often.
Especially this time of the year.
Let's tell it a story that people will understand.
And so, I want to probably go through some pretty basic verses.
You'll recognize it.
But read it with the Advent of love in mind.
Psalm 316.
For God, the creator of all, so loved the world.
He gave him his one and only son.
And whoever believes in him will not pray, but how he can love us.
Amen.
God, so loved the world.
And I love how John details this out.
Later on, 1 John 4, 19-12.
Let me read this to you.
This is him just taking a little deeper on it.
Because this is how God showed his love among us.
It's pretty clear.
This is how he saves his love.
He sent his one and only son into the world that we might live through him.
This is love.
Make that we have loved God.
Because he loved us and sent his son as an atoning sacrifice for us.
Friends, dear friends, since God so loved us, we also have to love one another.
No one has ever seen God.
But if we love one another, God lives in us and his love is made to preach to us.
And that's God's love is part.
His love is part, I think, is so important.
His love is made to preach to us.
So if we dress your feet, God's love, and we kind of tip it to ourselves,
we're not a thing that makes part about responding in love to others.
There's something incomplete.
There's something missing.
So God goes on.
I think we're supposed to experience God's love.
We don't have to understand his love for us.
We have to experience his love for us.
And one day is a response.
And I think it's kind of proportional.
So when we talk about growing in our faith throughout our lives,
I think this is one of the ways that happens.
The more we understand and experience God's love for us, for me,
then the more we're able and possibly even compelled to serve his love.
And the more we fear his love, the more complete his love, the worse.
And we talk to the experience of a cycle of that, and indeed talking about things without works is what?
But in some ways, in some ways, in some ways, the most love for us, in us, what we're experiencing,
it's incomplete until we take that next step to serve, to demonstrate it.
And what does that really look like?
Let's make it.
Let's make it a difference for somebody else.
And when you're doing that because you recognize the fact that you have so picked up its love,
you're so blessed, because you're the initial thing,
you're going to share that life with somebody else.
I think when we get matured in our faith,
you begin looking for opportunities for life.
Because you recognize,
there's something really good
about responding in love to somebody who has a need.
I have to think of it this way.
At least this has been my experience.
It's like it resonates with my soul.
It's more than just feels good.
If I'm going to be done,
it really matters.
But here's the thing.
Sometimes I do something and I'm like,
well, that was okay.
I didn't have to meet every day.
I didn't see any beauty.
I'm sure I didn't do all.
It was just something else to do.
I do it.
Whatever.
Because other times where I do something,
I think, oh, this is going to be more good.
This is going to rock the world.
This is going to truly help.
I don't know.
But here's what I love.
When I'm faithful in loving and serving,
I can leave all that with God.
And I'm telling you,
there's been some times in my life
where I failed later.
But that one thing I did
that I didn't even think twice about,
I had used it in a powerful way.
Because that's what happens.
It's not really as much about it.
It's certainly not about my life.
It's about huge love.
You know, John 4, verse 19,
I think it's something that's so well.
And this is a verse that you probably all know.
You probably all have it in your memory.
What's amazing is when God brings it
back to your memory.
Because it just says it.
We love because he first loved us.
So this morning,
one of the things we're going to do
is just search everybody's beauty.
And I even want to invite folks
who are watching online.
I understand there's a record drive online
watching this morning.
I want to invite you at home
to participate in this.
Because we're going to actually do this.
This is one of those moments
where we get to do
an application of the truth
by actually doing it.
And so Mike,
God is going to come up
and tell us a little bit
about some of the other things
that we can do.
But that is a closing prayer.
It's a closing setting.
We're all going to take just a few minutes
to pray for every one of these comments.
And I'll share a little bit more about that
after Mike describes
some of the other things.
Thank you.